Guide to the EOS: "Transactions of the American Geophysical Union" records, 1985-1989 MS 047
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
EOS: "Transactions of the American Geophysical Union" records
1985-1989
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Reiff, Patricia
MS 047
3.75 Linear Feet
This collection contains articles and book reviews submitted to the publication "Transactions of the American Geophysical Union." Also included are office records, correspondence, SPR news, cover and meeting reports related to this publication of the AGU.
Biographical Note
Dr. Patricia H. Reiff is a Professor in the Department of Physics and Astronomy at Rice University. She served as Editor of EOS: "Transactions of the American Geophysical Union" publication from 1986-1989. She is also a Fellow of the American Geophysical Union and Director of the Rice Space Institute.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains articles and book reviews submitted to the publication "Transactions of the American Geophysical Union." Dr. Patricia Reiff served as editor of this publication from 1985-1989, and the collection also contains office records, correspondence, SPR news, covers and meeting reports as they relate to her editorship of this publication.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift donated by Dr. Patricia Reiff, Editor, Solar-Planetary Relationships and EOS, in February of 1992.
Index Terms
Subjects
Earth sciences; Space sciences; Education
Document Types
articles; reviews (document genre); letters (correspondence); reports
- Series I: Correspondence, 1985-1989, 255943
  - American Geophysical Union, 1985, 255962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Book Review – General Information and Potential Review Books, 255961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invited Papers Not Yet Submitted, 255960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - EOS To DO, 255959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - EOS Form Letters, 255958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - EOS History Corner, 255957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - EOS To Do Logs, Part 1, 255956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - EOS To Do Logs, Part 2, 255955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - EOS Miscellaneous Email, Part 1, 255954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - EOS Miscellaneous Email, Part 2, 255953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, 1985, 255952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, January – March 1986, 255951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, April – June 1986, 255950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, July – December 1986, 255949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, January – June 1987, 255948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, July – December 1987, 255947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, January – April 1988, 255946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, May – December 1988, 255945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - EOS Chronological Correspondence, 1989, 255944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Series II: Solar Planetary Relations news, 1986-1988, 255926
  - SPR News. August 1986, 255942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - SPR News. October 1986, 255941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - SPR News. December 1986. Stern-Dungey Interview, 255940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SPR News. December – January, 1986-1987, 255939 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - SPR News. February 1987, 255938 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - SPR News. March 1987, 255937 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - SPR News. April 1987, 255936 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - SPR News. June 1987, 255935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - SPR News. July 1987, 255934 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - SPR News. September 1987, 255933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - SPR News. October 1987, 255932 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - SPR News. December 1987, 255931 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - SPR News. January 1988, 255930 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - SPR News. March 1988, 255929 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - SPR News. August 1988, 255928 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - SPR News. October 1988, 255927 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Series III: Articles, 1986-1989, 255867
  - Allen. February 1986 Storm. 1986, 255925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hines. 1986, 255924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Holzworth. 1986, 255923 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - News – Centaur Canceled. 1986, 255922 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Peacock – News from NSF. 1986, 255921 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rees. Comet. 1986, 255920 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Scarf "Comment" to Taylor. 1986, 255919 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Shawhan – SPR News. 1986, 255918 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Shea. "Cosmic Ray Cutoffs." 1986 – withdrawn, 255917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Taylor. Venus. 1986, 255916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Tsurutani and Mendis. 1986, 255915 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Viking-Potemra. 1986, 255914 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Electronic Subs. May 1986, 255913 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rogers Report. June 1986, 255912 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Manka. September 1986, 255911 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Manka/EOS Article on CDAW. December 1986, 255910 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chang. Tornado. 1987, 255909 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hines – Aida. 1987, 255908 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reinhard-Giotto. 1987 – withdrawn, 255907 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rossi. Solar Wind. 1987, 255906 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Scar. "Prospects for Detection." 1987, 255905 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Schunk and Sojka. "Ionospheric Climate…" 1987, 255904 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Romick. "CEDAR – An Aeronomy Initiative." January 1987, 255903 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Christensen. "CEDAR News." February 1987, 255902 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Donahue Flap. (Nothing published.) April 1987, 255901 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kroehl. "Great Magnetic Storm of 1986." July 1987, 255900 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Treinish. July 1987, 255899 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ulbrich and Holden. July 1987, 255898 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Akasofu-Gamble. August 1987, 255897 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bohlin. Solar Program. August 1987, 255896 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Holzer. September 1987, 255895 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Schmelz. International Solar Month. 1988, 255894 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Ahluwalia and Bolin. 1988, 255893 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Pinto. "South Atlantic…" 1988, 255892 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Schmidt et al. "Cluster and Soho." 1988, 255891 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Smith. CEDAR. 1988, 255890 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Spring Special Session. 1988, 255889 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tsunoda. 1988, 255888 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Winske and Gosling. 1988, 255887 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Peratt, "Magnetosphere-Ionosphere Interactions…" February 1988, 255886 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Feynman Obit. April 1988, 255885 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Swift, "Report on the NSF REU Program…" May 1988, 255884 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Roederer, "GEM: Geospace Environment Modeling." August 1988, 255883 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Burch et al. Yosemite. August 1988, 255882 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Scarf Obit. October 1988, 255881 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hirman, "Solar and Geomagnetic Activity…" October 1988, 255880 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lee, "Reconnection Model." December 1988, 255879 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Akasofu, "Future of Magnetospheric…" 1989, 255878 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Gonzalez, "Solar-Terrestrial Processes…" 1989, 255877 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Sojka, "Global Scale…" 1989, 255876 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Thrane. Forwarded to Cheng. 1989, 255875 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - EOS and SPR – Book Review. "Solar Flare Prediction." December 1986, 255874 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Goertz Book Review, "Computer Simulations of Space Plasmas." January 1987, 255873 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - EOS. Gordon Book Review. January 1987, 255872 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Hunten Book Review. August 1987, 255871 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Carbary and Meng. Book Review. October 1987, 255870 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Gary. Book Review. October 1987, 255869 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Dessler. Book Review. 1988, 255868 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Series IV: Covers, Meeting Reports, Fora, Reviews of Geophysics, 1986-1989, 255824
  - Kaufman cover. 1986, 255866 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stern. Art. 1986, withdrawn, 255865 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Saunders cover. September 1986, 255864 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hallinan cover. 1987, 255863 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Akasofu cover, EOS. May 1987, 255862 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Akasofu Shock cover. 1988, 255861 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Roper. Globmet Meeting Report. 1986, 255860 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Shea. IUGG Report: Cosmic Ray, Solar and Interplanetary Physics. February 1986, 255859 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dryer and Shea. Meeting Announcement. June 1986, 255858 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - EOS. Dryer and Shea. Meeting Report, "STIP Symposium on Retrospective Analyses…" Nov. 1986, 255857 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Joselyn. Meeting Report. "Solar Events and Their Influence…" December 1986, 255856 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Potemra. Meeting Report. 1987, 255855 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - DSUWG Meeting Report. January 1987, 255854 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gallagher. Meeting Report. September 1987, 255853 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Axford. COSPAR Meeting Summary. 1988, 255852 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Domingo. Meeting Report. 1988, 255851 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Foukal. Meeting Report. 1988, 255850 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Joselyn. "Solar Events…" SPR Meeting Report. 1988?, 255849 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Borovsky. Meeting Announcement. January 1988, 255848 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Meriwether. CEDAR Meeting Report. October 1988, 255847 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Siscoe. Auroral Physics Meeting Report. October 1988, 255846 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Akasofu. Emp. Forum. 1986, 255845 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Cowley Forum. 1986, 255844 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hunsucker Forum. 1986, 255843 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Intriligator Forum. 1986, 255842 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Singh Forum. 1986, 255841 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Zwickl Forum. 1986, 255840 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Baker Promotion Forum. 1987, 255839 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Eviatar Forum. 1987, 255838 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Forum. Peter Gary. March 1987, 255837 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - EOS Fraser-Smith Forum. April 1987, 255836 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ness-Smith Forum. June 1988, 255835 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Reviews of Geophysics. Chronological Correspondence .1987-1988, 255834 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Reviews General, 255833 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Reviews Editorship, 255832 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Reviews Foukal, Solar Electric Fields. 1988, 255831 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Reviews DE Issue. 1987, 255830 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Reviews ISEE Issue. 1988, 255829 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Reviews Birn and Hones, Plasma Sheet, no date, 255828 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Reviews Young. 1987, 255827 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Reviews Neugebauer. 1989, 255826 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Geophysical Research Publication Manual, 255825 (Box 3, Folder 42)